# Shashini Mayadunne

**Email**: shashini.mayadunne@gmail.com **Phone number**: 0410 468 546

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shashini-mayadunne

GitHub: https://github.com/Shash833

Address: 307-436/442 Huntingdale Road, Mount Waverley, Victoria 3149

\_\_\_\_\_

# **Professional Summary:**

Full Stack Web Developer with a strong academic background in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js and React.js after completing a Coding Bootcamp with Monash University.

Having been a successful Podiatrist for the past five years, the key skills that align with Web Development include problem solving, teamwork and relationship building.

Eager to further develop these skills and tackle challenges through a career in Web Development with a positive mindset and willingness to learn. Have also acquired the ability to be innovative and have attention to detail through a number of Web Development projects.

\_\_\_\_\_\_

# **Education:**

2020 Monash University Coding Bootcamp
Monash University & Trilogy Education

2011 - 2015 Bachelor of Health Sciences and Master of Podiatric Practice

La Trobe University

2005 - 2010 Secondary education and VCE

Glen Waverley Secondary College

\_\_\_\_\_

## **Skills and Attributes:**

## Problem Solving:

A career in podiatry has allowed this area to strengthen while diagnosing and formulating treatment plans for patients through utilising a solution oriented mindset.

As a web developer, completing projects has further developed problem solving skills while

overcoming any obstacles faced.

### • Work within a team:

As a podiatrist, working within a multidisciplinary team and other podiatrists to express ideas as well as appreciating input from other team members to achieve the team goal. As a web developer, working within a team of other web developers by sharing ideas and work load to build group projects.

### • Relationship building:

To build confidence with patients and the team through providing insightful professional advice.

As a web developer taking part in group projects, was able to develop a productive relationship with team members.

#### Attention to Detail:

Write clean and well commented code. Demonstrated during several individual and group projects where all functional requirements were met, and was easily integrated with other developer's code.

### • Innovation:

Enjoy focusing on creativity to build websites with aesthetic user interfaces. This is demonstrated in project repositories within the above GitHub profile.

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB: Have taken part in individual and group projects to create CLI and web applications with different functionalities implementing technologies. These are demonstrated within the GitHub profile linked above.

#### • Git:

Collaborated with a team during group projects utilising Git.

# **Experience:**

**July 2017-Current** Podiatrist - *TLC Health Care* 

**April 2016 - July 2017** Podiatrist - *Stawell Regional Health* 

April 2016 - July 2017Podiatrist - Healthcare2youJanuary - April 2016Podiatrist - FootPlus Podiatry

### Responsibilities/Achievements:

- Providing podiatric care to patients both autonomously and within a team setting.
- Complete podiatry assessments and thorough care plans for patients.
- Work collaboratively within multi-disciplinary teams to provide holistic care to patients. This
  involved providing podiatric input as well as considering other team member's ideas to
  formulate treatment plans.
- Ensure smooth running of the Primary Care and Podiatry departments with effective communication between team members and managers.
- Taken part in quality improvement projects to benefit the podiatry department and explore effective treatment options.
- Provide informational sessions for co-workers to share knowledge and provide education and create awareness in podiatric related care to help improve patient outcomes.

### **Referees:**

Available upon request